Guide to the Records of WNYU RG.39.5
New York University Archives
- Series V: Recorded Programs, 1968-1996; 20 Linear Feet in 14 record cartons, 3 LP boxes, 2 manuscript boxes, and 1 CD box.
  - Crucial Chaos: Abomination (Live), February 18, 1988 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0168, Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0596, Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0527)
  - Crucial Chaos: Super Touch and Murphy's Law, March 17, 1988 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0651)
  - Crucial Chaos: Bad Trip (Live Performance), April 14, 1988 (Box 10, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0001)
  - Crucial Chaos: Uppercut and Desperate Minds (Live), April 28, 1988 (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0224, Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0549)
  - Crucial Chaos: Toxic Zombies (Live), May 12, 1988 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0568)
  - Crucial Chaos: Maximum Penalty (Live), June 2, 1988 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0159)
  - Crucial Chaos: UK Subs, Broken Bones, Discharge, Token Entry, Kurt from Six and Violence (Interview), June 23, 1988 (Box 13, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0100)
  - Crucial Chaos: Token Entry, Ludichrist (Interviews), Upfront (Live) Part I, June 15, 1988 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0191)
  - Crucial Chaos: Zombie Squad (Live), July 21, 1988 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0662)
  - Crucial Chaos: SNFU (Interview) and Bugout Society (Live), August 4, 1988 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0188)
  - Crucial Chaos: Seizure (Live), September 1, 1988 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0622)
  - Crucial Chaos: Sticks and Stones (Live), September 15, 1988 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0626)
  - Crucial Chaos: SFA (Live), September 29, 1988 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0623)
  - Crucial Chaos: Life Sentence, November 17, 1988 (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0011)
  - Crucial Chaos: Leeway (Interview), January 19, 1989 (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0024)
  - Crucial Chaos: Face the Facts (Live), July 6, 1989 (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0058)
  - Crucial Chaos: Mr. Pickle (Live), August 3, 1989 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0158)
  - Crucial Chaos: Crib Death (Live), August 18, 1989 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0349)
  - Crucial Chaos: Misery (Live), August 18, 1989 (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0236)
  - Crucial Chaos: Bleeding Hemerroids (Live Performance), August 31, 1989 (Box 10, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0005)
  - Crucial Chaos: Functional Idiots (Live), September 14, 1989 (Box 16, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0588)
    Audio reel 39_5_0588 was identified as moldy in December, 2022. This item is currently isolated from other items by housing it in a polyethylene bag with a desiccated board and RH monitor strip. If this strip indicates an RH greater than 50%, contact the Preservation Department immediately. Do not open this packaging without contacting the Preservation Department.
  - Crucial Chaos: The Press (Live), October 26, 1989 (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0115)
    The host of this episode is Bruce.
  - Crucial Chaos: Resistance (Live), November 16, 1989 (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0240)
  - Crucial Chaos: The Elite (Live), December 7, 1989 (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0130)
  - Crucial Chaos: Crawl Pappy (Interview), February 8, 1990 (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0238)
  - Crucial Chaos: Nihilistics (Live and Interview), March 8, 1990 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0368, Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0271)
  - Crucial Chaos: Nothing Left (Live), April 12, 1990 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0606)
  - Crucial Chaos: Beef Trust (Live), May 3, 1990 (Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0518)
  - Crucial Chaos: Mark My Words (Live), May 17, 1990 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0154)
  - Crucial Chaos: Nutjob (Live), June 21, 1990 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0595, Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0069)
  - Crucial Chaos: Apocalypse, June 28, 1990 (Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0537)
  - Crucial Chaos: Apostates (Live), July 6, 1990 (Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0523)
  - Crucial Chaos: Wretched Ones Part II (Live), July 19, 1990 (Box 13, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0099)
  - Crucial Chaos: Entombed (Live), August 2, 1990 (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0078)
  - Crucial Chaos: Norman Bates and the Showerheads (Live), August 16, 1990 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0155)
  - Crucial Chaos: D Mize (Live), September 13, 1990 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0631)
  - Crucial Chaos: At All Cost (Live Performance), October 25, 1990 (Box 10, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0004)
  - Crucial Chaos: Urgent Fury (Live), November 15, 1990 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0571)
  - Crucial Chaos: SFA (Live), November 29, 1990 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0367)
  - Crucial Chaos: Born Against (Live), April 4, 1991 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0177, Box 22, Cd 39_5_0383, Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0534)
  - Crucial Chaos: No Escape, April 11, 1991 (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0068)
  - Crucial Chaos: Life Sentence (Live), October 17, 1991 (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0020)
  - Crucial Chaos: Breakdown (Live), September 24, 1992 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0189)
  - Crucial Chaos: Underdog, Undated (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0616)
  - In Touch: I'll Be You, Final Mix, September 14, 1987 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0362)
  - In Touch: Executive Slacks, circa December 1, 1989 (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0008)
    This episode was recorded with Athan.
  - Music View: The Fleshtones (Interview), 1980 (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0382)
    Duration: 00:25:05
    The hosts of this episode are Joanie Evenson and Mike Dugan.
  - Music View: XTC (Interview), 1980 (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0510)
    Duration: 00:17:10
  - Music View: dB's (Interview with Evan Davies and Suzie Albright), May 1, 1980 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0661)
  - Music View: Jonathan Richman, May 6, 1980 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0609)
  - Music View: Kid Creole, May 12, 1980 (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0030)
  - Music View: Jonathan Richman (Interview), May 16, 1980 (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0393)
    Duration: 00:21:54
    The host of this episode is Tammy.
  - Music View: Wreckless Eric, Suzie Albright, May 19, 1980 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0586)
  - Music View: The Feelies (Interview), June 2, 1980 (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0064, Box 22, Cd 39_5_0384)
    Duration: 00:13:44
    The hosts of this episode are Suzie Albright and Mike Dugan.
  - Music View: Kid Creole (Interview), August 2, 1980 (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0380)
    Duration: 00:25:51
  - Music View: Undertones (Interview), September 8, 1980 (Box 13, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0097)
  - Music View: Orchestral Manoeuvres in the Dark (Interview), October 10, 1981 (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0506)
    Duration: 00:23:56
  - Music View: Orchestral Manoeuvres in the Dark, Andy McClusky, November 25, 1981 (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0239)
  - Music View: Jools Holland (Interview), 1982 (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0406)
    Duration: 00:24:01
    The host of this episode is Tim Sommer.
  - Music View: The Revillos (Live and Interview), May 14, 1982 (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0148)
    This live set features the songs "Rock-a-Boom," "Voo Doo," and "Motorbike Beat." The host of this spisode is Tim Sommer.
  - Music View: Dead Kennedys (Interview), August 5, 1982 (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0408)
    Duration: 00:13:35
  - Music View: Thompson Twins (Live), February 18, 1983 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0647)
    Songs performed include "In the Name of Love," "Lies," and "Beach Culture."
  - Music View: Kevin Rowland, May 27, 1983 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0361)
  - Music View: Aztec Camera, August 1, 1983 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0589)
    Featuring the songs "Bach on Board," "Letters," and "Down the Dip."
  - Music View: Aztec Camera, October 10, 1983 (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0035)
  - Music View: The Smiths, 1984 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0572)
  - Music View: NY Rocker, January 11, 1984 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0604)
    Air Date: February 17, 1984
  - Music View: The Smiths (Interview), January 19, 1984 (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0405)
    Duration: 00:27:31
  - Music View: Chiefs of Relief, September 30, 1985 (Box 16, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0412)
    Audio reel 39_5_0412 was identified as moldy in December, 2022. This item is currently isolated from other items by housing it in a polyethylene bag with a desiccated board and RH monitor strip. If this strip indicates an RH greater than 50%, contact the Preservation Department immediately. Do not open this packaging without contacting the Preservation Department.
  - Music View: Blixa/Einsturzende Neubaten, October 21, 1985 (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0056)
  - Music View: Einsturzende Neubaten (Interview), October 21, 1985 (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0507)
    Duration: 00:20:06
  - Music View: Suicidal Tendencies, December 5, 1985 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0297)
  - Music View: The Dream Academy, December 6, 1985 (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0013)
  - Music View: Fear (Interview), 1986 (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0396)
    Duration: 00:29:10
    The host of this episode is Jon Fox
  - Music View/New Afternoon Show: Band of Outsiders (Interview), January 14, 1986 (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0402)
    Duration: 00:09:47
    The hosts of this episode are Leigh Lust and Jon Fox.
  - Music View: Willy De Ville, January 17, 1986 (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0014)
    The host of this episode is Jon Fox.
  - Music View: Angst (Interview), January 18, 1986 (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0397)
    Duration: 00:31:26
  - Music View: Social Distortion / Vandals, February 22, 1986 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0585)
  - Music View: Fear, March 15, 1986 (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0063)
  - Music View: Poi Dog Pondering (Live), September 19, 1987 (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0389)
    Duration: 00:14:35
  - Music View: Ruts DC, December 13, 1987 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0607)
  - Music View: Stranglers (Interview), October 3, 1989 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0576, Box 22, Cd 39_5_0409)
    Duration: 00:18:41
  - Music View: Richard Linklater (Interview), July 1, 1991 (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0400)
    Duration: 00:26:17
  - Music View: Dislocation Dance (Interview), Undated (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0391)
    Duration: 00:24:49
  - Music View: Frank Zappa, Undated (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0032)
  - Music View: Judy Wallace, Egyptians, Undated (Box 16, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0210)
  - Music View: Liquid Liquid (Interview), Undated (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0513)
    Duration: 00:32:50
  - Music View: Red Lorry Yellow Lorry, Undated (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0255)
  - Music View: XTC, Undated (Box 13, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0092)
  - New Afternoon Show: The Iguanas (Live), October 27, 1981 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0359)
  - New Afternoon Show: Feargal Sharkey, March 26, 1985 (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0136)
    The host of this episode is Emily.
  - New Afternoon Show: East Bay Ray, Klaus Fluoride (Live), November 14, 1985 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0300)
  - New Afternoon Show: Dramarama, January 13, 1986 (Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0280)
    The host of this episode is Judy.
  - New Afternoon Show: Band of Outsiders (Live), January 14, 1986 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0332)
  - New Afternoon Show: Dead Milkmen, January 15, 1986 (Box 16, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0207)
  - New Afternoon Show: Raunch Hands (Live), January 16, 1986 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0635)
  - New Afternoon Show: Live Skull (Live), January 17, 1986 (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0047)
  - New Afternoon Show: Handsome Dick / Dictators, January 22, 1986 (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0038)
    The host of this episode is Bernard.
  - New Afternoon Show: Tailgators, January 31, 1986 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0582)
  - New Afternoon Show: Reducers (Live), March 21, 1986 (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0123)
  - New Afternoon Show: The Reducers (Interview), March 21, 1986 (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0503)
    Duration: 00:11:30
  - New Afternoon Show: Mojo Nixon and Skip Roper (Live), May 2, 1986 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0613)
  - New Afternoon Show: Soul Asylum (Live), May 2, 1986 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0174)
  - New Afternoon Show: The Alter Boys, June 13, 1986 (Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0543)
  - New Afternoon Show: Blood Circus (Live, Interview), June 29, 1986 (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0515)
    The host of this episode is Colleen.
  - New Afternoon Show: Death of Samantha, August 6, 1986 (Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0548)
  - New Afternoon Show: APB, October, 1986 (Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0542)
    The host of this episode is Joel.
  - New Afternoon Show: Doctor and the Medics (Interview), October 2, 1986 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0663)
  - New Afternoon Show: Died Pretty, October 16,1986 (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0254)
  - New Afternoon Show: Richard Lloyd, October 17, 1986 (Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0272)
  - New Afternoon Show: Flaming Lips, October 22, 1986 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0184)
  - New Afternoon Show: The Flaming Lips (Interview), October 22, 1986 (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0395)
    Duration: 00:17:23
  - New Afternoon Show: Richard Barone of the Bongos (Live), October 23, 1986 (Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0268)
  - New Afternoon Show: Dead Boys (Interview), October 31, 1986 (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0145, Box 22, Cd 39_5_0504)
    Duration: 00:17:57
    Hosted by Jon Fox. Featuring an unreleased original mix of "Sonic Reducer" and the 4 Track demo of a Cheetah Chrome song, "All the Way Down."
  - New Afternoon Show: The Lucy Show, Mark and Rob (Live), December 9, 1986 (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0043)
    Featuring the songs "Remembrances," "Melody," "Part of Me Now," and "I Ride Alone / Do I Ride?"
  - New Afternoon Show: Wire (Interview), 1987 (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0390)
    Duration: 00:30:49
  - New Afternoon Show: Lemonheads (Interview), January 8, 1987 (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0019, Box 22, Cd 39_5_0499)
    Duration: 00:15:56
  - New Afternoon Show: Band of Outsiders, January 29, 1987 (Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0519)
  - New Afternoon Show: Deep 6, February 27, 1987 (Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0524)
  - New Afternoon Show: Splat Cats, March 5, 1987 (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0151)
  - New Afternoon Show: DOA with Hum, March 12, 1987 (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0065)
  - New Afternoon Show: k.d. lang, May 4, 1987 (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0247)
  - New Afternoon Show: Executive Slacks, May 7, 1987 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0190)
  - New Afternoon Show: Not for Sale, May 14, 1987 (Box 16, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0195)
  - New Afternoon Show: Downy Mildew, June 18, 1987 (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0116)
  - New Afternoon Show: Wire, July, 1987 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0583)
  - New Afternoon Show: Electric Peace, July 7, 1987 (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0242)
  - New Afternoon Show: Drivin' and Cryin', The Chills (Interview), July 15, 1987 (Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0552, Box 22, Cd 39_5_0379)
  - New Afternoon Show: Butthole Surfers, July 28, 1987 (Box 13, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0110, 39_5_0111)
  - New Afternoon Show: Clint Ruin, Jim Thirwell, Foetus (Interview), August 28, 1987 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0574)
  - New Afternoon Show: Foetus (Interview), August 28, 1987 (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0375)
    Duration: 00:27:44
    The host of this episode is J.G. Thirwell.
  - New Afternoon Show: Live Skull (Interview), September 19, 1987 (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0009, Box 22, Cd 39_5_0511)
    Duration: 00:20:15
  - New Afternoon Show: Membranes (Live), September 24, 1987 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0157)
  - New Afternoon Show: Sharky's Machine, October 8, 1987 (Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0289)
  - New Afternoon Show: The Iguanas (Interview), October 27, 1987 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0360)
  - New Afternoon Show: That Petrol Emotion, November 13, 1987 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0649)
  - New Afternoon Show: Screaming Blue Messiahs and Bill Carter (Interview), December 8, 1987 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0617)
  - New Afternoon Show: The Leather Nun (Interview), December 9, 1987 (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0023)
  - New Afternoon Show: The Shaved Pigs (Interview), December 15, 1987 (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0118)
  - New Afternoon Show: Swans (Live set and Interview), December 17, 1987 (Box 13, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0109)
  - New Afternoon Show: Alien Sex Fiend, December 18, 1987 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0164, 39_5_0167)
  - New Afternoon Show: Gibson Bros. (Interview), January 8, 1988 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0170)
  - New Afternoon Show: Braineaters (Interview), January 13, 1988 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0165)
  - New Afternoon Show: Flower (Live Set and Interview), January 29, 1988 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0171, Box 10, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0002)
  - New Afternoon Show: Zero Boys (Live), March 4, 1988 (Box 13, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0096)
  - New Afternoon Show: Luxuria, Howard Devoto / Noko, March 30, 1988 (Box 16, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0356, 39_5_0357)
  - New Afternoon Show: These Immortal Souls, April 4, 1988 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0580)
  - New Afternoon Show: Drivin'-n-Cryin' (Acoustic Set), April 15, 1988 (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0137)
    Boren on guitar, Tim Nielson on mandolin, Kevin Kinney on guitar and vocals
  - New Afternoon Show: Shaved Pigs, April 21, 1988 (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0126)
  - New Afternoon Show: Eugene Chadbourne, April 22, 1988 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0310, 39_5_0315)
  - New Afternoon Show: Blurt (Live), April 27, 1988 (Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0533)
  - New Afternoon Show: Vernon Reid and Corey Glover from Living Colour, April 29, 1988 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0591, Box 22, Cd 39_5_0498)
    Duration: 00:31:34
    The host of this episode is Marlene.
  - New Afternoon Show: Fall, Brix Smith, Mark, May 5, 1988 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0313)
  - New Afternoon Show: Soul Asylum's Karl Mueller, May 6, 1988 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0655)
  - New Afternoon Show: Didjits (Live set and Interview), May 18, 1988 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0160)
  - New Afternoon Show: Stump, May 31, 1988 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0650)
  - New Afternoon Show: Jazz Butcher (Live), June 2, 1988 (Box 13, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0112)
  - New Afternoon Show: Sugarcubes (Interview), June 15, 1988 (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0142, Box 22, Cd 39_5_0376, Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0282)
    Duration: 00:32:34
    The host of this episode is Leigh Lust; Includes Jesus and Mary Chain mix of "Birthday"
  - New Afternoon Show: Jon Langford and Marc Riley (Interview), June 24, 1988 (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0377, 39_5_0378, Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0660)
  - New Afternoon Show: Yo La Tengo and dB's, August 5, 1988 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0584)
  - New Afternoon Show: Dream Syndicate, August 17, 1986 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0319)
    The hosts of this episode are Bernard and Hugh Foley.
  - New Afternoon Show: The Fluid, September 1, 1988 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0614)
  - New Afternoon Show: Reverb Motherfuckers, September 2, 1988 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0601)
  - New Afternoon Show: Pagan Babies (Interview), September 9, 1988 (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0225)
  - New Afternoon Show: Shaved Pigs (Interview), September 30, 1988 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0619)
  - New Afternoon Show: Scrawl (Live, Interview), October 7, 1988 (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0141)
  - New Afternoon Show: Let's Active, October 19, 1988 (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0041)
  - New Afternoon Show: New Model Army, Justin Sullivan (Live), November 2, 1988 (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0233)
  - New Afternoon Show: Dream Syndicate, November 16, 1988 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0330)
  - New Afternoon Show: Lucinda Williams, circa December 8, 1988 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0307)
  - New Afternoon Show: Datura Seeds, December 9, 1988 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0200)
  - New Afternoon Show: Red Lorry Yellow Lorry, Chris Reed, December 15, 1988 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0350)
  - New Afternoon Show: Bruce from A-Bones and Michael from Raunch Hands, January 12, 1989 (Box 16, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0197)
  - New Afternoon Show: Tackhead, January 18, 1989 (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0039, Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0290)
  - New Afternoon Show: Murphy's Law "Back With a Bong" (Interview), January 26, 1989 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0610)
  - New Afternoon Show: Bush Tetras, February 2, 1989 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0306)
  - New Afternoon Show: The Cows (Live set and Interview), February 24, 1989 (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0037)
  - New Afternoon Show: The Dwarves (Live and Interview), March 23, 1989 (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0253)
  - New Afternoon Show: Killing Joke, March 30, 1989 (Box 16, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0410)
    Audio reel 39_5_0410 was identified as moldy in December, 2022. This item is currently isolated from other items by housing it in a polyethylene bag with a desiccated board and RH monitor strip. If this strip indicates an RH greater than 50%, contact the Preservation Department immediately. Do not open this packaging without contacting the Preservation Department.
  - New Afternoon Show: Christmas (Interview), March 31, 1989 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0327)
  - New Afternoon Show: Legendary Pink Dots, Edward Kaspell with Lust, April 4, 1989 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0325)
  - New Afternoon Show: That Petrol Emotion, April 5, 1989 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0642)
  - New Afternoon Show: Dryin' and Cryin' (Live), April 11, 1989 (Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0281)
  - New Afternoon Show: SWA, May 5, 1989 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0169, Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0292)
  - New Afternoon Show: Alice Donut (Interview), May 12, 1989 (Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0547)
  - New Afternoon Show: Ed Hall (Live), May 15, 1989 (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0131, 39_5_0135)
    The host of this episode is Emily. The band members of Ed Hall include Gary Chester (Guitar, Vocals), Larry Strub (Bass, Vocals), and Kevin Whitley (Drums, Vocals).
  - New Afternoon Show: Poi Dog Pondering (Live), May 15, 1989 (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0251)
  - New Afternoon Show: Laughing Hyenas (Interview), May 23, 1989 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0605)
  - New Afternoon Show: Wire (Interview), June 1, 1989 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0594)
  - New Afternoon Show: Band of Susans (Interview), June 9, 1989 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0317)
  - New Afternoon Show: SNFU, June 9, 1989 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0629)
  - New Afternoon Show: Prong, June 16, 1989 (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0040)
  - New Afternoon Show: Blood Circus (Live, Interview), June 29, 1989 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0638)
  - New Afternoon Show: Peter Stampfell, July 20, 1989 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0320)